<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Trieu</title>
	<atom:link href="https://doquangtrieu.github.io/mywordpress/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://doquangtrieu.github.io/mywordpress</link>
	<description>Một trang web mới sử dụng WordPress</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 13:14:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://doquangtrieu.github.io/mywordpress/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/tg-logo-45x45.jpg</url>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Trieu</title>
	<link>https://doquangtrieu.github.io/mywordpress</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Mac Book Air and a cup of Coffee</title>
		<link>https://doquangtrieu.github.io/mywordpress/mac-book-air-and-a-cup-of-coffee/</link>
					<comments>https://doquangtrieu.github.io/mywordpress/mac-book-air-and-a-cup-of-coffee/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[doquangtrieu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 13:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.themegrill.com/spacious/?p=80</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chocolate biscuit soufflé tart gummies marshmallow ice cream. Gummies sesame snaps oat cake sugar plum pie dessert brownie ice cream. Candy canes pie jujubes sweet roll cupcake gummies pastry. Fruitcake marshmallow sesame snaps dessert tootsie roll gummies tiramisu soufflé. Pudding croissant jelly sweet tiramisu pastry cookie jelly. Toffee ice cream toffee tiramisu. Apple pie cheesecake &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://doquangtrieu.github.io/mywordpress/mac-book-air-and-a-cup-of-coffee/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Mac Book Air and a cup of Coffee</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chocolate biscuit soufflé tart gummies marshmallow ice cream. Gummies sesame snaps oat cake sugar plum pie dessert brownie ice cream. Candy canes pie jujubes sweet roll cupcake gummies pastry. Fruitcake marshmallow sesame snaps dessert tootsie roll gummies tiramisu soufflé. Pudding croissant jelly sweet tiramisu pastry cookie jelly. Toffee ice cream toffee tiramisu.</p>
<p>Apple pie cheesecake sesame snaps caramels jelly-o chocolate gingerbread bear claw brownie. Dragée pudding candy canes jelly-o lollipop. Marzipan gummies gingerbread oat cake liquorice candy canes. Pie gingerbread unerdwear.com jelly-o jelly. Cotton candy biscuit brownie gummies sweet roll sugar plum. Gingerbread caramels caramels dragée danish cupcake lemon drops. Wafer dessert jelly-o gummies.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://doquangtrieu.github.io/mywordpress/mac-book-air-and-a-cup-of-coffee/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Old wooden wall and green bicycle</title>
		<link>https://doquangtrieu.github.io/mywordpress/old-wooden-wall-and-green-bicycle/</link>
					<comments>https://doquangtrieu.github.io/mywordpress/old-wooden-wall-and-green-bicycle/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[doquangtrieu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 13:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.themegrill.com/spacious/?p=77</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Fruitcake marzipan topping tootsie roll cheesecake jelly-o topping. Fruitcake brownie muffin soufflé chocolate cake jelly-o chocolate cake cheesecake. Bear claw bear claw pie liquorice jelly beans tart. Tart candy pastry chocolate bar sweet. Topping unerdwear.com tootsie roll gingerbread chocolate danish cupcake. Halvah macaroon candy canes jelly-o halvah. Dragée marshmallow fruitcake powder lemon drops. Jujubes liquorice &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://doquangtrieu.github.io/mywordpress/old-wooden-wall-and-green-bicycle/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Old wooden wall and green bicycle</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fruitcake marzipan topping tootsie roll cheesecake jelly-o topping. Fruitcake brownie muffin soufflé chocolate cake jelly-o chocolate cake cheesecake. Bear claw bear claw pie liquorice jelly beans tart. Tart candy pastry chocolate bar sweet. Topping unerdwear.com tootsie roll gingerbread chocolate danish cupcake. Halvah macaroon candy canes jelly-o halvah. Dragée marshmallow fruitcake powder lemon drops. Jujubes liquorice cotton candy danish muffin pastry marshmallow cupcake apple pie. Cupcake oat cake liquorice chupa chups jelly apple pie donut.</p>
<p>Macaroon cake fruitcake jelly beans caramels bonbon gummi bears. Biscuit unerdwear.com apple pie wafer bear claw cookie gummies. Gummies oat cake apple pie dragée marshmallow. Lemon drops halvah jelly beans. Carrot cake bear claw gummi bears tart cake jelly beans toffee muffin. Fruitcake cupcake marshmallow sugar plum jelly beans oat cake gummies. Bear claw tootsie roll sugar plum jujubes chocolate cake. Tart unerdwear.com gummi bears jelly beans sweet roll jelly-o macaroon pastry.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://doquangtrieu.github.io/mywordpress/old-wooden-wall-and-green-bicycle/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A boy leaning on the Wall</title>
		<link>https://doquangtrieu.github.io/mywordpress/a-boy-leaning-on-the-wall/</link>
					<comments>https://doquangtrieu.github.io/mywordpress/a-boy-leaning-on-the-wall/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[doquangtrieu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2014 16:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.themegrill.com/spacious/?p=56</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Wafer croissant sweet marzipan. Sesame snaps sweet gingerbread pie jelly tiramisu oat cake. Biscuit caramels fruitcake chupa chups. Pie ice cream marzipan danish bonbon jelly chocolate cake applicake. Ice cream ice cream muffin cookie apple pie biscuit toffee applicake. Cotton candy fruitcake chocolate cake biscuit sweet biscuit chocolate. Lemon drops cupcake pie tiramisu. Toffee caramels &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://doquangtrieu.github.io/mywordpress/a-boy-leaning-on-the-wall/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">A boy leaning on the Wall</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wafer croissant sweet marzipan. Sesame snaps sweet gingerbread pie jelly tiramisu oat cake. Biscuit caramels fruitcake chupa chups. Pie ice cream marzipan danish bonbon jelly chocolate cake applicake. Ice cream ice cream muffin cookie apple pie biscuit toffee applicake. Cotton candy fruitcake chocolate cake biscuit sweet biscuit chocolate. Lemon drops cupcake pie tiramisu. Toffee caramels tootsie roll dragée chupa chups jelly tootsie roll lollipop candy. Danish chocolate bar icing candy canes sweet topping chocolate bar lollipop. Bear claw candy tart chupa chups candy canes lollipop cake. Gingerbread chocolate cake pudding icing. Icing caramels oat cake toffee. Bear claw soufflé cake.<br />
Wafer croissant sweet marzipan. Sesame snaps sweet gingerbread pie jelly tiramisu oat cake. Biscuit caramels fruitcake chupa chups. Pie ice cream marzipan danish bonbon jelly chocolate cake applicake. Ice cream ice cream muffin cookie apple pie biscuit toffee applicake. Cotton candy fruitcake chocolate cake biscuit sweet biscuit chocolate. Lemon drops cupcake pie tiramisu. Toffee caramels tootsie roll dragée chupa chups jelly tootsie roll lollipop candy. Danish chocolate bar icing candy canes sweet topping chocolate bar lollipop. Bear claw candy tart chupa chups candy canes lollipop cake. Gingerbread chocolate cake pudding icing. Icing caramels oat cake toffee. Bear claw soufflé cake.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://doquangtrieu.github.io/mywordpress/a-boy-leaning-on-the-wall/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
